MICHAEL GAUTHIER

Victoria, BC • 236-969-6116 • migauth@outlook.com • github.com/migauth • linkedin.com/in/migauth

Professional Summary

Full stack web developer blending expertise in inclusive education and creative practices. Emphasizes the creation of effective, adaptable, and test-focused code. Values community engagement and effective communication. Demonstrates outstanding leadership and organizational capabilities.

Skills

JavaScript, HTML, CSS SQL fundamentals Python

React proficiency Ruby on Rails NodeJS

API Integration Git, Github Jest, Cypress

Education

Diploma, Full Stack Web Development: 05/2024

Lighthouse Labs - Victoria, BC (Remote online)

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Art Education: 06/2014

Concordia University - Montreal, Quebec

Employment

Braille specialist and educational assistant, 03/2020 to Current

Greater Victoria School District 61 - Victoria, BC

• Providing inclusive education and curriculum adaptations for blind students.

Out of school care provider, 09/2019 to 03/2020

Fairfield Gonzales Community Association - Victoria, BC

• Provided care for children grades 1-4. Groups of 15-20 students. Focused care for child with autism.

Bindery department assistant/Front desk clerk, 04/2018 to 08/2019

Island Blue Print - Victoria, BC

- Use of computers, printers, scanners, and various cutting and binding machines. Customer service.
- Extensive use of Microsoft Word, Excel, Acrobat Pro, and Photoshop.